<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sudo chown ethan-hanlon</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on sudo chown ethan-hanlon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Ethan Hanlon, 2021</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>[Email] me@ethan-hanlon.xyz Probably the best way to reach me. [LinkedIn] https://www.linkedin.com/in/ethan-hanlon-6688491a6/ I accept connections with people I&amp;rsquo;ve met or had enough interaction with to consider a professional contact. [Discord] If we&amp;rsquo;re scheduled to meet, you can email me for my Discord. I try to keep it for people who really need to communicate with me that way. [Social Media] See about page I usually respond to DMs, but would prefer to talk through email if you&amp;rsquo;re reaching out of the blue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there My name is Ethan Hanlon and this is my personal blog, sudo chown ethan-hanlon. I&amp;rsquo;ll use it to talk about whatever stuff is on my mind - technical stuff, thoughts, travels, whatnot. I&amp;rsquo;ll try to post weekly updates, so definitely stay tuned.
I&amp;rsquo;m a Computer Science student at San Francisco State University and I have a passion for using programming to build cool stuff and advance justice in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, World!</title>
      <link>/posts/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hello/</guid>
      <description>This is my first post on this blog. I&amp;rsquo;ll be posting about tech, my own travels and projects, and whatever other stuff goes through my mind. I&amp;rsquo;ll try to deliver weekly updates, so stay tuned! Check out the about and showcase sections if you want more info about me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showcase</title>
      <link>/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/showcase/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s some of the stuff I&amp;rsquo;ve made. I&amp;rsquo;ll update this as I go along.
Markup Master [Status] Soon to be live [Platform] Web [Website] https://markupmaster.xyz [Discord] https://discord.gg/Ar3vguwN3f Markup Master is a GPT-Based HTML, CSS, and JavaScript generator. It&amp;rsquo;s a pretty awesome system - you just tell it what you want to make (for example, &amp;ldquo;A pong clone&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;A blog with a modern UI&amp;rdquo;) and it builds you all the code you need to get started.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
